Inside. In the kitchen.
Are you all right?
An accident. Sorry to trouble you.
May I come in?
Of course!
Sugar, milk?
No need. Thank you.
Delicious!
What's wrong?
Don Eduardo is here!
So good to see you!
I'd shake your hand, but...
Look at you! Mountain man!
You look like ZZ Top!
Clean up for Don Eduardo! Go wash, shave!
Oh, sure!
I'm sorry, Don Eduardo.
Go!
Keep the mustache and the soul patch.
It looks good.
Yes, Don Eduardo.
You're sure you don't want breakfast?
The eggs are fresh from this morning.
How are Mateo's teeth doing? Better?
Yes! Your dentist worked so hard!
Matti used to be up all night
with the pain.
Now he sleeps like a baby.
Thanks to you, Don Eduardo.
That's good, Sylvia.
And the goats?
From your hometown?
They don't miss the mountains?
They're fine.
We're expecting two more next month.
You sent for more?
Cabritos. Babies.
You're almost finished. I'll make more.
You're sure about breakfast?
Just coffee is fine.