Black holes are considered to be
the hellmouths of the universe.
[Wissenschaftler]  Schwarze Löcher gelten
als die Höllenschlunde des Universums.
Those who fall inside disappear.
Wer hineinfällt, verschwindet.
Forever.
Für immer.
But whereto?
Aber wohin?
What lies behind a black hole?
Was liegt hinter einem schwarzen Loch?
WHERE (WHEN) IS MIKKEL?
Verschwinden dort mit den Dingen
auch Raum und Zeit?
Along with things,
do space and time also vanish there?
Or would space and time
Oder wären Raum und Zeit
in einem ewigen Kreis
miteinander verbunden?
be tied together
and be part of an endless cycle?
Und was, wenn das,
was aus der Vergangenheit kommt,
What if everything that came from the past
were influenced by the future?
durch die Zukunft beeinflusst wäre?
Tick-tock.
Tick, tack.