Inside. In the kitchen.
Rein. In die Küche.
Ja.
Wo sind Sie?
Keine Ahnung.
Ich bin nur...
nach Norden gegangen. Zwei Stunden.
Überquerte einen Fluss. Vor einer Stunde.
Sah Sie jemand?
Nein.
Weiter so.
Das ist Salamanca-Gebiet.
Alle suchen nach Ihnen.
Damit meine ich alle.
Auch die Federales.
Ist es erledigt?
Ja. Er ist tot.
Da waren auch ein paar...
normale Leute...
im Haus, alte Leute.
Und die?
Darüber weiß ich nichts.
Wenn wir aufhören,
die Batterie aus dem Handy nehmen.
Dann nach Norden.
Außer Sicht bleiben.
Ich bereite ein Versteck für Sie vor.
In einer Stunde
die Batterie wieder einlegen.
Ich sage Ihnen, wo Sie hinsollen.
Don Eduardo!
Are you all right?
Ist alles klar?
An accident. Sorry to trouble you.
Ein Unfall. Es tut mir leid.
May I come in?
Darf ich?
Of course!
Natürlich!
Sugar, milk?
Zucker? Milch?
No need. Thank you.
Nein. Danke.
Delicious!
Köstlich!
What's wrong?
Was ist los?
Don Eduardo is here!
So good to see you!
I'd shake your hand, but...
Look at you! Mountain man!
You look like ZZ Top!
Clean up for Don Eduardo! Go wash, shave!
Oh, sure!
I'm sorry, Don Eduardo.
Go!
Keep the mustache and the soul patch.
It looks good.
Yes, Don Eduardo.
You're sure you don't want breakfast?
The eggs are fresh from this morning.
How are Mateo's teeth doing? Better?
Yes! Your dentist worked so hard!
Matti used to be up all night
with the pain.
Now he sleeps like a baby.
Thanks to you, Don Eduardo.
That's good, Sylvia.
And the goats?
From your hometown?
They don't miss the mountains?
They're fine.
We're expecting two more next month.
You sent for more?
Cabritos. Babies.
You're almost finished. I'll make more.
You're sure about breakfast?
Just coffee is fine.